(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
右に進むか... 左の道なら...
Should I go right... If I take the left path...
解は？ チャンスか？
What's the answer? Is it a chance?
リスクがでかい リスクが小さい
Huge risk... Small risk...
やっぱり右？ いや左か... どうする
Right after all? No, left...? What do I do?!
人を過度に信じないように
Try not to trust people too much.
愛さないように
Try not to love too much.
期待しないように
Try not to expect too much.
かと言って角が立たないように
But try not to make waves either.
気取らぬように
Try not to act stuck-up.
目立たぬように
Try not to stand out.
誰一人傷つけぬように
Try not to hurt a single person.
虐めぬように
Try not to bully anyone.
殺さぬように
Try not to kill anyone.
かと言って偽善がバレないように
But try not to let your hypocrisy show.
威張らないように
Try not to be arrogant.
軽いジョークやリップサービスも忘れぬように
Try not to forget light jokes and lip service.
どんな時も笑って愛嬌振り撒くように
Smile and sprinkle charm everywhere, no matter the time.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration.
兎角言わずにちゃんと召し上がれ
Just eat it up properly without complaining.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration.
食わず嫌いはちゃんと直さなきゃ
You have to fix your pickiness properly.
頭空っぽその後に
Empty your head, and after that...
残る心が本物なら
If the heart that remains is real...
きっと君だって同じ事
Surely, you're just the same.
「そこで一つ、ここいらで一つ」
"So here's one, and here's another."
いや
No,
元の位置が収らさるように
so that the original position is settled,
話さるように 分からるように
so that it is spoken, so that it is understood,
でも競った口は閉ざさるように
but so that the pursed mouth is closed,
笑わすように 笑われるように
so as to make them laugh, so as to be laughed at,
人ちゃんと敬うように 崇めるように 讃えるように
so as to properly respect, revere, and praise people,
でもやっぱ有耶無耶にならないように
but essentially, so it doesn't become vague,
ふざけないように
so as not to mess around.
集団参加の終止形
The final form of group participation,
またへーこらへーこら言っちゃって
bowing and scraping again,
あれ前髪超絶最強じゃん
"Hey, your bangs are totally the best!"
とかどうでもいいのに言っちゃって
saying things I couldn't care less about.
毎朝毎晩もう限界
Every morning, every night, I'm at my limit.
宗教的社会の集団リンチ
Mass lynching in a religious society.
でも決して発狂しないように
But try absolutely not to go insane.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration.
兎角言わずに来な 愛は君を汚す
Don't complain, just come. Love will dirty you.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration.
立つ鳥の後 濁す 濁す 後
Leaving a mess behind as the bird flies away.
初めはあんな大層な大言壮語を並べたが
At first, you lined up such grand, bombastic words,
いやいや嫌よ嫌よも好きのうち
No, no, "I hate it, I hate it" means I like it?
いや早しかし今日が初めてで
No, wait, but today is the first time,
こんなとはね 君センスあるよ
I didn't expect this. You have sense.
恋する季節にビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration in the season of love.
恋する気持ちでビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration with feelings of love.
F.U.C.K.Y.O.U
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration.
皆が望む理想に憧れて
Longing for the ideal that everyone desires.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration.
個性や自我は全部焼き払い
Burn away all individuality and ego.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration.
欲やエゴは殺して土に埋め
Kill greed and ego and bury them in the earth.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration.
僕は大人にやっとなったよママ
I've finally become an adult, Mama.
明日もきっとこの先も
Surely tomorrow and in the future too,
地獄は続くどこまでも
hell will continue on endlessly.
あ だからどうか今だけは
Ah, so please, just for now,
子供の頃の気持ちのままで
let me stay with the feelings of my childhood,
一切を忘れてやってこうぜ
let's forget everything and do it.
あ 思い出した あの時の
Ah, I remembered. That time...
生真面目そうな...
looking so serious...
やっぱいいや
Actually, never mind.
お…サイコロ
Oh... A die.
5が出た
It's a five.
ん？何これ？
Hmm? What is this?
椅子？
A chair?
After the war 世の常
After the war, it's the way of the world.
崩れた跡しない
No trace left after the collapse.
肝心なのは So na Money
What's essential is that money.
出し抜いて Survive
Outwit them and survive.
行き着く先は Heaven or Hell
The destination is Heaven or Hell.
この世界なる
In this world,
たった一つ 勝者こそが正義
there is only one rule: the winner is justice.
女は度胸
A woman needs courage.
焦らさせるの アイツを
I'll keep him in suspense.
やれること
Whatever I can do,
なんだってやる
I'll do anything.
アタシは 賭け狂いのQueen
I am the compulsive gambling Queen.
Deal with the devil 見透かして
Deal with the devil, see through it.
アタシのものにする
I'll make it mine.
あなたの髪の 一本まで全部
Every single strand of your hair, everything.
A million dollars, I'd say raise
震えてるわよ坊や
You're shaking, boy.
降ろさせはしないわ
I won't let you fold.
Deal with the devil uh 興奮
Deal with the devil, ooh, the excitement.
たまらないわ Thrill
The thrill is unbearable.
誰にも触らせない このMoney
I won't let anyone touch this money.
A million dollars, I'd say raise
さあカモン 覚悟決めて
Come on, steel your resolve.
震え高ぶれ My heart
Tremble and rage, my heart.
欲しがるようじゃまだBaby
If you just want it, you're still a baby.
誰にも負けない 感じさせて Love Honey
I won't lose to anyone, let me feel it, Love Honey.
あなたの内緒側
Your secret side...
Ah, oh my god.
仕掛けて罠にハメるわ
I'll set a trap and snare you in it.
油断誘うのよ
Inviting you to let your guard down.
思考を止めて楽しめ
Stop thinking and just enjoy it.
何も知らないような顔で
With a face like you know nothing,
落とすわあなたを
I will bring you down.
どうせ明日は予定調和のつまらない日々
Tomorrow is just another boring day of pre-established harmony anyway.
でもだって変に重ねない
But even so, I won't play it safe,
どんな小さなズルだって
Even the smallest cheat,
アタシの目は誤魔化されないわ
My eyes won't be fooled.
I'm beginning of the race
相手するなら覚悟決めて
If you're going to take me on, be prepared.
粛清してあげる
I'll purge you.
狙った獲物は逃さない
I won't let my targeted prey escape.
唇濡らして
Wet your lips,
いただくわ全て
I'll take everything.
ダイヤのジャックで手が揃うわ
With the Jack of Diamonds, my hand is complete.
笑みは殺し始末だけ
Kill the smile, it's just the end.
アタシのポーカーフェイスは It's perfect
My poker face is It's perfect.
一部の隙も見せたりしないわ
I won't show even a single gap.
視線感じて
Feeling the gaze,
お望みなら最後まで
If you wish, until the very end.
見てばかりいないでアタシが教えてあげる
Don't just watch, I'll teach you.
負けるのが怖いの？ Risk?
Are you afraid of losing? The risk?
夢消えた列車だ
It's a train where dreams vanished.
手を取って変に透かして
Take my hand and act all coy,
アタシのものにする
I'll make it mine.
あなたの髪の一本まで全部
Every single strand of your hair, all of it.
I'm beginning of the race
震え待ってるのよ Oh yeah
Trembling and waiting, oh yeah.
行くところまで行くわ
I'll go as far as I can go.
Dealを取って 捨て身の Bluff
Take the deal, a desperate bluff.
躊躇わない 恐れない
I won't hesitate, I won't fear.
誰にも触らせないこの Money
I won't let anyone touch this money.
I'm beginning of the race
覚悟決めて
Make up your mind.
灰になるまで撃って
Shoot until it turns to ash.
弾けるようじゃね まだ Baby
If you're popping off, you're still a baby.
誰にも負けない感じさせて Love me Honey
Make me feel like I won't lose to anyone... Love me Honey.
おっと…あれ？椅子…なくなっちゃった
Oops... huh? The chair... is gone.
もう少し座らせて欲しかった…
I wanted to sit a little longer...
はーい みんな！
Hiii, everyone!
見えてる？聞こえてる？
Can you see me? Can you hear me?
ホロライブ所属の癒し系ハーフエルフ
Hololive's healing half-elf,
アキロゼこと アキ・ローゼンタールです！
AkiRose, aka Aki Rosenthal!
ハロハロハロー！アローナ！
Hallo hallo hallo! Alona!
えー 今回の #アキロゼ生誕祭2026 へ
Um, to this AkiRose Birthday Festival 2026...
ようこそ！
Welcome!
早速ね なんか色々行われていたんですが
Things were happening right from the start, but...
一体今回のライブはどうなっちゃうのか
I wonder what on earth will happen in this live...
ぜひ 最後まで必見！
Please, it's a must-watch until the end!
お見逃しなく お願いします
Don't miss it, please.
今回のライブのハッシュタグは
The hashtag for this live is...
#アキロゼ生誕祭2026
#AkiRoseBirthdayFestival2026
こちらをつけて Xに沢山ポストしてね
Use this and post lots on X, okay?
もちろん可愛い…スクショ！
Of course, cute... screenshots!
アハーン
Ahaan~
えー 沢山撮って 合わせて投稿してください
Um, please take lots and post them together.
ライブが終わったあと アキロゼ見に行きます
After the live ends, AkiRose will go look at them.
見てね
Watch me, okay?
あ チャンネル登録もよろしくね！
Ah, please subscribe to the channel too!
オッケー？ 曲行って？ はい ありがと
Okay? Go to the song? Yes, thanks.
ほっ ん？なんだ？何なにナニ？
Ho. Hm? What is it? What what what?
え？うおーん…
Eh? Whoa...
ていうか ここ どこなんだろう？
By the way, where is this place?
お？あんなとこにルーレットがある
Oh? There's a roulette over there.
え 回るのかな？
Eh, I wonder if it spins?
おっ え！回った！えー すごい！回った！
Oh, eh! It spun! Eh, amazing! It spun!
え？
Eh?
何？何？
What? What?
どうなっちゃうの？
What's going to happen?
え？
Eh?
あ...
Ah...
え？
Eh?
ピース？
Peace?
あ？
Ah?
ん？
Hm?
なんだ？
What is it?
Unhappy 悩める人の
Unhappy, for those who worry,
Unlucky 隣去る者も
Unlucky, even those leaving my side,
Be happy 合間縫い目指せよ
Be happy, aim for the gaps,
生きているんだし
Since we are alive.
ねえ 恐れた過去も
Hey, the feared past too,
退屈な未来も
And the boring future too,
カウンセリング？ やれやれ
Counseling? Good grief.
古今東西 Peace Peace
All times and places, Peace Peace.
Unhappy
Unlucky
Be happy
UNDEAD!!
ねえねえねえ 何だかどうして
Hey hey hey, somehow why,
戦ってるようなそんな気がするの
I feel like I'm fighting something.
やられない 痛くもない
Can't be beaten, doesn't even hurt.
過去の自分
My past self,
もうとっくに死んでる
Is already long dead.
透明な亡霊だ
It's a transparent ghost,
幼気で痛い記憶の奥
Deep in innocent and painful memories.
残念 もういないのに あれ？
Too bad, it's already gone... huh?
そっちがアイロニーね
That part is the irony.
透かされてるのは今の自分
The one being seen through is my current self.
なんせ消えない減ってる
Because it won't disappear, it's decreasing,
いいえ 弱コンプレックス
No, a weak complex.
取り憑かれてるみたい
Looks like I'm possessed.
巻きついたまま まだ
Wrapped around, still,
離れない
It won't let go,
ありし日の自分
My self from days gone by.
UNDEAD!!
死んじゃいない
I'm not dead,
終わってないの連鎖
A chain of not ending.
生きてるかどうかとか
Whether I'm alive or not,
終わり続ける葛藤だ
It's a conflict that keeps ending.
不幸に甘んじて
Content with misfortune,
満足するなよ
Don't be satisfied.
幸せになろうとしないなんて
Not trying to be happy...
虚だ
...is empty.
この世 この世は
This world, this world is,
奇奇怪怪ファンタジー
A strange, strange fantasy.
次は鬼が出るか
Next, will a demon appear?
蛇が出るか
Or will a snake appear?
出会って会って
Meeting, meeting,
やっと始まる物語
Finally the story begins.
去っていった化け物が
The monster that left,
そっと及第 Peace Peace
Quietly passing grade, Peace Peace.
Past and future
Can't change the past
Live for the future
ねえ 何だかどうして
Hey, somehow why,
未来に難と難の不穏モナ
Difficulty upon difficulty in the future...
私的な予感がして
I have a personal premonition.
もう随分生きてる
I've been alive for quite a while,
石棺とテンプレートで触書
Sarcophagus and template writing,
突発的な出来事の気配もない
No sign of sudden events.
残念 積んだ経験も
Too bad, accumulated experience too,
因果関係が崩れた神話
Myths where causality collapsed.
度 退屈な進化
Degrees, boring evolution,
飽きちゃった
I got bored,
誰と死んだ？
Who did I die with?
なんせ滞っていくガイダンス
Because the guidance is stagnating,
滑るコンプライアンス
Slipping compliance,
透かされていくみたい
Looks like I'm being seen through.
推測して
Guess it,
あれもこれも
This and that,
どれも同じ味がする
Everything tastes the same.
UNDEAD!!
死んじゃいない
I'm not dead,
終わってないの連鎖
A chain of not ending.
いつの世も過去も
In any age, the past,
未来も今にあるんだ
And the future exist in the now.
生きていることを
Being alive,
愚直に果たせよ
Fulfill it honestly.
目指せ Happy End
Aim for a Happy End.
UNDEAD!!
死んじゃいない
I'm not dead,
お前に言ってるんだ
I'm talking to you.
幸せを諦めてしまう
Giving up on happiness,
那由多である
Is countless.
ただ苦しみに慣れて
Just getting used to suffering,
耐えているだけじゃ
And just enduring it,
死んでるも同然
Is as good as being dead.
屍のアンデッド
A corpse's undead.
Unhappy 悩める人の
Unhappy, for those who worry,
Unlucky 隣去る者も
Unlucky, even those leaving my side,
Be happy 絶えず目指せよ
Be happy, aim for it constantly,
生きているんだろ
You are alive, right?
不相応に光るも
Even if it shines disproportionately,
幸せになるのも
Becoming happy,
もう全部全部お前だ
It's all, all up to you.
古今東西 Peace Peace
All times and places, Peace Peace.
死んだ埋葬
Dead burial,
Peace Peace
Past and future
Can't change the past
Live for the future
きっと慣れた所
Surely the place you got used to,
いつもの良い事
The usual good things,
この化け物ばかりの
Of this monster-filled,
物語
Story.
愛♡スクリーム！
Ai Scream!
教えてもっと あなたのこと
Tell me more about you,
Hear me, yum, more, more
聞かせてもっと あなたの声
Let me hear more of your voice,
Hear me, yum, more, more
こんなドキドキ もう制御できない
I can't control this pounding anymore,
All I need is you
友達は卒業
Graduating from being friends,
運命の私 見つけてほしいの
I want you to find the destined me.
One!
見つめる作戦
A staring strategy.
認めちゃえば
If I just admit it,
Fall in Love
止められない
I can't stop it,
Yeah yeah yeah この恋この愛で
Yeah yeah yeah, with this love, this affection,
めめめめ 溶けちゃうよ
Me-me-me-me, I'm going to melt.
ねねねね 気づいて My Darling
Hey-hey-hey-hey, notice me, My Darling.
届け 大好き
Reach you, I love you!
Ai-Ai-Ice Cream Scream 叫びましょう
Ai-Ai-Ice Cream, Scream, let's shout it out!
Scream Ai-Scream Okay?
Ai-Ai-Ice Cream Scream 叫びましょう
Ai-Ai-Ice Cream, Scream, let's shout it out!
Scream Ai-Scream
バルルちゃん！
Baruru-chan!
はーい！
Yees!
何が好き？
What do you like?
チョコミントよりも あなた！
More than choco-mint... You!
ブルルちゃん！
Bururu-chan!
はーい！
Yees!
何が好き？
What do you like?
ストロベリーフレーバーよりも あなた！
More than strawberry flavor... You!
アキちゃん！
Aki-chan!
はーい！
Yees!
何が好き？
What do you like?
クッキー＆クリームよりも あなた！
More than cookies & cream... You!
みんな！
Everyone!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
もちろん大好き アイスクリーム！
Of course, we love Ice Cream (Ai-Scream)!
止められない
I can't stop it,
Yeah yeah yeah この恋この愛で
Yeah yeah yeah, with this love, this affection,
めめめめ 溶けちゃうよ
Me-me-me-me, I'm going to melt.
ねねねね 気づいて My Darling
Hey-hey-hey-hey, notice me, My Darling.
今日だけ 大好き
Just for today, I love you!
Ai-Ai-Ice Cream Scream 叫びましょう
Ai-Ai-Ice Cream, Scream, let's shout it out!
Scream Ai-Scream Okay?
Ai-Ai-Ice Cream Scream 叫びましょう
Ai-Ai-Ice Cream, Scream, let's shout it out!
Scream Ai-Scream
お願い見つけて My Darling
Please find me, My Darling.
お願い気づいて My Darling
Please notice me, My Darling.
勇気を出して
Muster up your courage,
近づく作戦
A strategy to get closer.
手と手が触れて
Our hands touch,
Fall in Love
止められない
I can't stop it,
Yeah yeah yeah この恋この愛で
Yeah yeah yeah, with this love, this affection,
めめめめ 溶けちゃうよ
Me-me-me-me, I'm going to melt.
ねねねね 気づいて My Darling
Hey-hey-hey-hey, notice me, My Darling.
それは あなた
That is... you.
Ai-Ai-Ice Cream Scream 叫びましょう
Ai-Ai-Ice Cream, Scream, let's shout it out!
Scream Ai-Scream Okay?
Ai-Ai-Ice Cream Scream 叫びましょう
Ai-Ai-Ice Cream, Scream, let's shout it out!
Scream Ai-Scream
Ai-Ai-Ice Cream Scream 叫びましょう
Ai-Ai-Ice Cream, Scream, let's shout it out!
Scream Ai-Scream Are you ready?
Ai-Ai-Ice Cream Scream 叫びましょう
Ai-Ai-Ice Cream, Scream, let's shout it out!
Scream Ai-Scream
La la la...
おぉ 元気もらって 面白くって
Oh, someone who gives energy, is funny,
オレンジで
is orange,
シャンパンコール得意な人
and is good at champagne calls...
いないかなー？
Is there anyone like that?
それ俺やないかーい！
That's me, isn't it?!
イケナイ太陽
Ikenai Taiyou (Sinful Sun)
Na na na na na na na-na
ちょっとでいいから
Just a little bit is fine,
見せてくれないか
won't you show me?
お前のセクシー・フェロモンで
With your sexy pheromones,
オレ メロメロ
make me fall madly in love.
Ah 触れちゃいそう
Ah, I'm about to touch,
でもイケナイの
but I shouldn't.
徐々に高なる鼓動 止められないわ
My heart beats faster and faster, I can't stop it.
交わす言葉の記憶 遠く
The memories of our exchanged words fade away,
口元の動きに 揺れ動く
swayed by the movement of your lips.
ABC 続かない そんなんじゃダメじゃない
ABC, it doesn't continue, isn't that no good?
だってココロの奥は違うじゃない
Because deep inside the heart, it's different, right?
オレの青春そんなもんじゃない
My youth isn't something like that.
熱く奥で果てたいよ
I want to finish hotly deep inside.
きっとキミじゃなきゃヤダよ
Surely, I don't want anyone but you.
オレはイケナイ太陽
I am a naughty sun.
Na na na...
赤い糸なんて絵空事
The red string of fate is just a pipe dream.
でも下心でさえ信じたいの
But I want to believe even in ulterior motives.
オレは正しい キミも正しい
I am right, and you are right too.
とにかくもう左右されないぜ
Anyway, I won't be swayed anymore.
騙し騙され胸疼く
Deceiving and being deceived, my chest aches.
下芝居が夜盛り上げる
Cheap tricks liven up the night.
息が耳に触れた二人 Ah...
Breath touched the ear, the two of us, ah...
ABC 続かない そんなんじゃダメじゃない
ABC, it doesn't continue, isn't that no good?
だってココロの奥は違うじゃない
Because deep inside the heart, it's different, right?
私の青春そんなもんじゃない
My youth isn't something like that.
熱く奥で果てたいよ
I want to finish hotly deep inside.
きっとキミじゃなきゃヤダよ
Surely, I don't want anyone but you.
私イケナイ太陽
I am a naughty sun.
交わす言葉の記憶遠く
The memories of exchanged words are distant.
口元の動きに揺れる
Swaying to the movement of the lips.
濡れた髪を撫でた そして Ah...
Stroked the wet hair, and then, ah...
ABC 続かない そんなんじゃダメじゃない
ABC, it doesn't continue, isn't that no good?
だってココロの奥は違うじゃない
Because deep inside the heart, it's different, right?
オレの青春そんなもんじゃない
My youth isn't something like that.
熱く奥で果てたいよ
I want to finish hotly deep inside.
きっとキミじゃなきゃヤダよ
Surely, I don't want anyone but you.
オレはイケナイ太陽
I am a naughty sun.
絡み合う糸はキミと
The intertwining thread is with you...
オレを結ぶ赤い糸
...the red thread that ties me.
Na na na...
はぁ…はぁ…
(Panting)
みんな！来てくれてありがとうー！
Everyone! Thanks for coming!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
ということで お友達が来てくれたので せっかくなので自己紹介してもらおうと思います！
So, since my friends are here, I'd like them to introduce themselves!
まずは ぷるるちんから！
First up, Pururu-chin!
はーい！天使と悪魔のハーフ プルプルエンジェルデビル 天杉ぷるるです！
Hi! Half Angel, Half Devil, Puru-Puru Angel Devil, I'm Amasugi Pururu!
ぷるるだよー！おはぷるー！
It's Pururu! Ohapuru!
アキパイセン お誕生日おめでとう！
Aki-paisen, Happy Birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
いやー とっても楽しかったねー！
Man, that was so much fun!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
そして続いて かるびちゃん！
And next up, Karubi-chan!
はーい！お肉の国のお姫様 赤見かるびです！
Hi! Princess of the Meat Kingdom, I'm Akami Karubi!
アキロゼ 誕生日おめでとう！
AkiRose, Happy Birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
いいね ライブって 友達とライブ初めてだからさ マジで嬉しかったよ
Live shows are great. It's my first time doing a live with friends, so I was really happy.
ありがとう呼んでくれて
Thanks for inviting me.
またやろうぜ！
Let's do it again!
またやろう！
Let's do it!
そして最後に ずずさん！
And finally, Zuzu-san!
はーい！僕のこと知らない人いると思うんで 自己紹介だけさせてください！
Hi! I think some people don't know me, so let me just introduce myself!
雨降ってザーザー 少女時代はGee Gee
Rain falls zaa-zaa, Girls' Generation goes Gee Gee!
俺の名前は ズズズズズ… ズズでございます！
My name is Zu-Zu-Zu-Zu-Zu... I am Zuzu!
いやー お誕生日おめでとう！
Man, Happy Birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
どうもありがとう！
Thank you so much!
今日は本当にありがとう！
Thank you so much for today!
Thank you! Thank you!
賑やかで楽しかった！
It was lively and so much fun!
まるで...
It's almost as if...
この世界で
in this world,
二人だけみたいだね
we are the only two people.
なんて少しだけ
I just had a little...
夢を見てしまっただけ
...dream, that's all.
つま先に月明かり
Moonlight on my toes,
花束の香り
the scent of a bouquet.
弓に触れる指
Fingers touching the bow.
さよならもう行かなきゃ
Goodbye, I must go now,
何もかも忘れて
forgetting absolutely everything.
ガラスの上を裸足のまま歩く
Walking barefoot on top of glass.
痛むごとに血が流れて落ちていく
With every pain, blood flows and falls.
お願いその赤い足跡を辿って
Please, follow those red footprints...
会いに来て
...and come to see me.
錆びたプールに放たれていく金魚
A goldfish released into a rusted pool.
屑籠の中隠した林檎
An apple hidden inside a trash can.
萎びた君の肌に残る傷跡
The scars remaining on your withered skin.
犬のように泳いだ迷子
A lost child swimming like a dog.
どこにいるの
Where are you?
何をしてるの
What are you doing?
ここで見てるよ
I'm watching here.
この世は間違いで満たそう
Let's fill this world with mistakes.
そばにいてよ
Stay by my side.
遊びに行こうよ
Let's go play.
どこにいるの
Where are you?
ガラスの上を裸足のまま歩く
Walking barefoot on top of glass.
痛むごとに血が流れて落ちていく
With every pain, blood flows and falls.
お願いその赤い足跡を辿って
Please, follow those red footprints...
会いに来て
...and come to see me.
まるでこの世界で二人だけみたいだね
It's almost as if we are the only two people in this world.
なんて少しだけ夢を見てしまっただけ
I just had a little dream, that's all.
さあ、選択の時だ
Now, it is time to choose.
コイン？
A coin?
このコインは...
This coin is...
はぁ...そうか。
Hah... I see.
君はそっちなんだね。
So you're on that side.
そっち？
That side?
ここに座って。
Sit here.
え？
Eh?
この後は...
What happens next...
君次第だよ。
is up to you.
忘れられないのはこの目のせい
It's this eye's fault I can't forget
赤く残る過ち 甘噛みの跡
The mistake remains red, a trace of a playful bite
溢れ出す愛は止め処もない
The overflowing love is endless
誰もいない間に悪魔を探そう
Let's look for the devil while no one is here
作り笑いはこの耳のせい
The fake smile is this ear's fault
深い壁の中から呼びかける声
A voice calling out from within the deep walls
Whisper Whisper Whisper まだ触らせない
Whisper Whisper Whisper, I won't let you touch yet
この檻を抜け出して悪魔は賭ける
Escaping this cage, the devil makes a bet
鏡の前でこの口のせい
In front of the mirror, it's this mouth's fault
伝えたい言葉さえ噛み殺す夜
A night where I stifle even the words I want to say
Whisper Whisper Whisper まだ打ち明けない
Whisper Whisper Whisper, I won't confess yet
神様を裏切って悪魔と過ごす
Betraying God to spend time with the devil
アイマイミー夢見ていたい貴方に
I, my, me, I want to keep dreaming of you
そっと気付かせてあげたいだけ
I just want to make you realize softly
Oh 貴方にも
Oh, to you too
消えない傷を隠したい
I want to hide the indelible scars
貴方にそっと悩ませてあげたいだけ
I just want to make you worry a little
Oh 貴方にも
Oh, to you too
悪魔を探す
I search for the devil
作り笑いはこの耳のせい
The fake smile is this ear's fault
深い壁の中から呼びかける声
A voice calling out from within the deep walls
Whisper Whisper Whisper まだ触らせない
Whisper Whisper Whisper, I won't let you touch yet
この檻を抜け出して悪魔は賭ける
Escaping this cage, the devil makes a bet
鏡の前でこの口のせい
In front of the mirror, it's this mouth's fault
伝えたい言葉さえ噛み殺す夜
A night where I stifle even the words I want to say
Whisper Whisper Whisper まだ打ち明けない
Whisper Whisper Whisper, I won't confess yet
神様を裏切って悪魔と過ごす
Betraying God to spend time with the devil
好き嫌い常識 I don't care 吹き飛ばせば
Likes, dislikes, common sense, I don't care, just blow it away
かかってこい Majority アタシに負けはなし
Bring it on, Majority, I never lose
ここまでって引かれたそのボーダー誰のルール？
Who's rule decided that border drawn up to here?
あの日乗り越えた Weak heart
The weak heart I overcame that day
強くなったアタシが笑い飛ばすだけ
Now that I'm stronger, I just laugh it off
言いたいことは言う
I say what I want to say
やりたくないことはしない
I don't do what I don't want to do
悪意気にしない
I don't care about malice
みんな違うの当然だし
It's natural that everyone is different
アタシも変わらない譲れないの
I won't change either, I won't yield
自分だけは
myself.
Ready ready set I want to be free
明日のことはもう言わない
I won't talk about tomorrow anymore
それじゃ何も変えられない
That won't change anything
Ready ready set I want to be strong
守りたい自分肯定
I want to protect my self-affirmation
生きてるんだアタシ
I am living
運命決めてるんだだし
Because I'm deciding my fate
声上げて生まれたバースから選んできたんだ
I've been choosing since the birth I cried out for
思い出せ アタシはアタシだ 他の誰でもない
Remember, I am me, nobody else
何一つもない 嘘じゃないない
There's nothing, it's not a lie
大事なファンに
To my important fans
好き嫌い常識 I don't care 吹き飛ばせば
Likes, dislikes, common sense, I don't care, just blow it away
Filter 外して この lyric かまして
Take off the filter, drop this lyric
わからす挑発
A provocation to make you understand
下向いて舌打ちからの HA
Looking down, clicking my tongue, then HA
Excuse me?
イカせてあげる Ah
I'll let you go, Ah.
やってきた感慨な
The deep emotion that has arrived.
アタシがついてるから
Because I'm here with you.
Everybody say I want to be free
この美徳習慣 全部黙らす Show
This virtuous custom, a show to silence it all.
目覚ませ起きろ
Wake up, get up!
生きてるんだだし
Since I'm alive.
ねえ 生きてるんだだし
Hey, since I'm alive.
生まれたその時から選んできたんだ思い出せ
Remember, I chose this from the moment I was born.
アタシはアタシだ
I am me.
不可能なことなど何一つもない そうじゃないの
There's nothing impossible, isn't that right?
生まれたその時から選んできたんだ思い出せ
Remember, I chose this from the moment I was born.
貴方は貴方だ
You are you.
不可能なことなど何一つもない そうじゃないの
There's nothing impossible, isn't that right?
愛いっぱい自分に
Full of love for myself.
好き嫌い常識 I don't care ぶっ飛ばせ
Likes, dislikes, common sense, I don't care, blast them away!
Again 好き嫌い常識 I don't care ぶっ飛ばせ
Again, likes, dislikes, common sense, I don't care, blast them away!
流れてく時の中ででも
Even within the flowing time,
気だるさがほらグルグル廻って
look, the lethargy spins round and round.
私から離れる心も見えないわ
I can't even see my heart leaving me.
そう知らない
I really don't know.
自分から動くこともなく
Without moving on my own,
時の隙間に流され続けて
I continue to be swept away in the gaps of time.
知らないわ周りのことなど
I don't know anything about what's around me.
私は私それだけ
I am me, that is all.
夢見てる？なにも見てない？
Am I dreaming? Am I seeing nothing?
語るも無駄な自分の言葉
My own words are useless to speak.
悲しむなんて疲れるだけよ
Being sad just makes me tired.
何も感じず過ごせばいいの
It's fine if I spend time feeling nothing.
戸惑う言葉与えられても
Even if given confusing words,
自分の心ただ上の空
my heart is just absent-minded.
もし私から動くのならば
If I were to move on my own,
すべて変えるのなら黒にする
if I could change everything, I'd turn it black.
こんな自分に未来はあるの？
Does such a self have a future?
こんな世界に私はいるの？
Am I existing in such a world?
今切ないの？今悲しいの？
Is it painful now? Is it sad now?
自分の事もわからないまま
While not even understanding myself.
歩むことさえ疲れるだけよ
Even walking just tires me out.
人のことなど知りもしないわ
I don't know anything about others.
こんな私も変われるのなら
If even I can change,
もし変われるのなら白になる
if I can change, I'll become white.
流れてく時の中ででも
Even within the flowing time,
気だるさがほらグルグル廻って
look, the lethargy spins round and round.
私から離れる心も見えないわ
I can't even see my heart leaving me.
そう知らない
I really don't know.
自分から動くこともなく
Without moving on my own,
時の隙間に流され続けて
I continue to be swept away in the gaps of time.
知らないわ周りのことなど
I don't know anything about what's around me.
私は私それだけ
I am me, that is all.
夢見てる？なにも見てない？
Am I dreaming? Am I seeing nothing?
語るも無駄な自分の言葉
My own words are useless to speak.
何もわからず過ごせばいいの
Is it fine to just live understanding nothing?
戸惑う言葉
Even if confusing words
与えられても
are given to me,
自分の心
my own heart
ただ上の空
is just absent-minded.
もし私から
If, from me,
動くのならば
I were to move,
すべて変えるのなら
if I were to change everything,
黒にする
I'll turn it black.
動くのならば
If I move,
if I move,
すべて壊すわ
I'll destroy everything.
悲しむならば
If I grieve,
if I grieve,
私の心
can my heart
白く変われる？
turn white?
あなたのことも
About you,
私のことも
about me,
すべてのことも
about everything,
まだ知らないの
I still don't know.
重い瞼を
If I opened
開けたのならば
my heavy eyelids,
すべて壊すのなら
if I am to destroy everything,
黒になれ
turn black!
いつか君が
Someday, the light of love
瞳に灯す
you light in your eyes
愛の光が
will cross time,
時を超えて
and surely destroy one thing
滅び急ぐ
in the world's dream
世界の夢を
that rushes towards ruin.
確かにひとつ
It will surely destroy one.
壊すだろう
It will destroy it.
躊躇いを
Swallow down
飲み干して
your hesitation.
君が望むものは何？
What is it that you wish for?
こんな欲深い
Is there a tomorrow
憧れの
at the destination
行方に
of such greedy aspiration,
儚い
so fleeting?
明日はあるの？
Is there a tomorrow?
子供の頃夢に見てた
Like the ancient magic I saw in dreams as a child,
古の魔法のように
like the ancient magic,
闇さえ砕く力で
with power to smash even the darkness,
微笑む君に会いたい
I want to meet the smiling you.
怯えるこの手の中には
Inside these frightened hands,
手折られた花の勇気
is the courage of a plucked flower.
想いだけが頼るすべて
Feelings are all I rely on.
光を呼び覚ます
Awakening the light,
願い
is my wish.
いつか君も
Someday, you too
誰かのために
will surely wish for strong power
強い力を
for someone's sake.
望むのだろう
You will surely wish for it.
愛が胸を
On the night love
捕らえた夜に
captured your heart,
未知の言葉が
unknown words
生まれて来る
are born.
迷わずに
If I can go
行けるなら
without hesitation,
心が砕けてもいいわ
it's fine if my heart breaks.
いつも目の前の
I want a spell
悲しみに
to confront the sadness
立ち向かうための
always before my eyes.
呪文が欲しい
I want a spell.
君はまだ夢見る記憶
You are still a dreaming memory.
私は眠らない明日
I am the sleepless tomorrow.
二人が出会う奇跡を
I will move forward to win
勝ち取るために進むわ
the miracle of us meeting.
怯えるこの手の中には
Inside these frightened hands,
手折られた花の刃
is the blade of a plucked flower.
想いだけが生きるすべて
Feelings are all that live.
心に振りかざす
Brandish in my heart,
願い
my wish.
囚われた太陽の
Of the captive sun...
輝く
...shining.
不思議の国の本が好きだった頃
When I loved books about Wonderland,
願いはきっと叶うと
that wishes would surely come true...
教えるお伽噺を信じた
...I believed the fairy tales that taught me so.
光と影の中
In the light and shadow.
静かに咲き乱れていた
Quietly blooming in profusion,
古の魔法を優しく
the ancient magic gently...
世界を変える力が
...whispers that the power to change the world...
その手にあると囁く
...is in your hands.
終わらない夢を見よう
Let's dream an endless dream.
君と行く時の中で
In the time I go with you,
想いだけが生きる全て
feelings are everything that lives.
命を作るのは
What creates life is...
願い
...a wish.
ワーッ！
Waaah!
アキちゃん！
Aki-chan!
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
ありがとう！イェーイ！
Thank you! Yeaah!
今日は来てくれてありがとうございます。
Thank you for coming today.
こちらこそですよ。
The pleasure is ours.
呼んでくれてありがとう。
Thanks for inviting us.
実はね、二人を呼んだのにちょっと理由があって。
Actually, there's a reason why I invited you two.
お、なんだなんだ？
Oh, what is it?
前に、アキロゼの4周年の時に3人で...
Before, at AkiRoze's 4th anniversary, the three of us...
Kalafinaさんの曲、歌わせてもらったんだっけ。
...sang a Kalafina song together.
やりましたね。
We did, didn't we.
めっちゃ良かったやつね。
It was really good.
ハーモニーがね。
The harmony, right?
もうね、ミオちゃんの歌も大好きだし、AZKiちゃんの歌も大好きだし...
I just love Mio-chan's singing, and AZKi-chan's singing too...
もうそこね、忘れられないの。
...and I can't forget that moment.
わかる。
I get it.
忘れない。
I won't forget it.
めっちゃわかる？
You really get it?
だからもう一回、このライブステージで、3人で歌いたくて...
So I wanted to sing with the three of us on this live stage one more time...
今日は来てもらいました！
...so I had you come today!
嬉しい！ありがとう！
I'm happy! Thank you!
だから、ま、これからは、これを機に...
So, well, taking this opportunity...
もっと何か3人で歌ったりとか...
...to sing more with the three of us...
何かそういうの挑戦できたらめっちゃ嬉しいなって。
...I'd be really happy if we could challenge things like that.
いいですか？
Is it okay?
ね、ハーモニーを重ねていきましょうよ。
Let's layer our harmonies together.
えー、いいの！？
Eh, really!?
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
何かユニット名とか欲しいな。
I kind of want a unit name or something.
あ、確かに欲しいな。
Ah, I definitely want one.
えー、なんだろう？
Eh, what would it be?
え、何かちょっと世界目指せるぐらいのさ...
Eh, something like, we could aim for the world...
世界！？
The world!?
ユニットにして...
...making it a unit...
世界のコンサートをしようよ。
...let's do a world concert.
やりたい！
I want to do it!
世界に轟く...
Roaring to the world...
何かをね、したいということで。
...doing something big, you mean.
そう、3人でライブとか、なんかアコースティックとか...
Yes, a live with the three of us, or like an acoustic set...
なんかオーケストラライブとか。
...or an orchestra live.
え、よくないですか？
Eh, isn't that nice?
そんなことをしてみたい。
I want to try doing things like that.
ね、我らならできるかもしれない！
Hey, maybe we can do it!
やったろう！
Let's do it!
お願いします！
Please!
ついていく！お願いします！
I'll follow! Please!
あれ？これはいったい何ですか？
Huh? What on earth is this?
お？もしかして...
Oh? Could it be...
このライブでみんなからの...
...from everyone at this live...
なんかいいパワーで...
...some good power...
なんかいいパワー！？なんか今来てる！？
Some good power!? Is something coming now!?
いいのあるじゃんそれ。
That's a good one.
なんだよそのパワー！
What is that power!
こちらがなんと、完成しました！
This has, surprisingly, been completed!
わーっ！なんだそれ！？
Waaah! What is that!?
実は...
Actually...
この後...
After this...
アキロゼの新曲が...
AkiRoze's new song...
出ます！
Will be released!
わーっ！
Waaaah!
こちら、ま、今回の...
This, well, this time's...
ライブの、ま、テーマというか...
...live's, well, theme or...
壮大なテーマがあるんですけれども...
...there's a grand theme, but...
そちらが詰まったような楽曲になっています。
...it has become a song packed with that.
そして、ライブ終わりの日付が変わる時にリリースしますので...
And, it will be released when the date changes after the live ends, so...
是非聴いてください！
...please definitely listen to it!
いいね！みんな聴くぞ！
Nice! Everyone listen!
はーい。
Ye-es.
じゃあ次の曲に行きますか？
Then, shall we go to the next song?
次の曲？
Next song?
新曲のお披露目？
New song reveal?
なんだって！？
What!?
しちゃいます！
I'll do it!
わーっ！
Waaaah!
もう新曲のお披露目...え、今からってこと？
New song reveal already... eh, you mean right now?
今から、頑張ります。
Right now, I'll do my best.
もう最後まで見逃せないですね！
Can't miss it until the very end, huh!
楽しみだ。
I'm looking forward to it.
じゃあアキちゃん頑張ってね！
Then Aki-chan, good luck!
ありがとう！またね！
Thank you! See you later!
またねー！
See ya!
魅惑の言葉の裏面に忍ばせた
Hidden on the flip side of those enchanting words,
1mgのスパイス
Is 1mg of spice.
たちまち華麗な指先で彩る
Instantly colored by brilliant fingertips,
本日のダイス
Today's dice roll.
当たり見てた興じてちゃ
If you're just amused watching for a win,
生き残れないでしょう
You won't be able to survive, will you?
率直に言ってその全てが欲しい
To put it frankly, I want it all.
一人勝ちにオールイン
Going all-in on a solo victory.
どうなっちゃってもいいじゃない
It doesn't matter what happens, does it?
際限なんてないじゃない
There are no limits, are there?
翻弄して 翻弄されて
Trifling with you, being trifled with...
ゾクゾク
It's thrilling.
喰らっちゃっても本望でしょう
Even if you take a hit, it's what you wanted, right?
最低だって滾るでしょう
Even at the worst, it gets your blood boiling, doesn't it?
見透かして 見透かされて
Seeing through me, being seen through...
Yeah yeah 終わりはない
Yeah yeah, there is no end.
高鳴るこの全てがノンフィクション
This heart-pounding everything is non-fiction.
嗜むはずでも たまには飲みすぎて
I should only dabble, but sometimes I drink too much,
一回休み
Skip one turn.
周りもざわつく 思わぬうたた寝で
The room buzzes at my unexpected dozing off,
二回休み
Skip two turns.
切れる頭と勘だけじゃ
With just a sharp mind and intuition,
手に入らないもの
You can't get your hands on this.
そこでいて満たされるならいい
If you're satisfied just being there, that's fine.
命懸けで楽しむわ Yeah yeah yeah!
But I'll bet my life and enjoy it! Yeah yeah yeah!
天地は案外違いない
Heaven and earth are surprisingly alike.
この通り命乞い
Just like this, begging for life.
だけどモノポリー
But it's Monopoly,
されど王将里
Yet still the royal path.
キめる想いで 今宵も私は強い
With a resolved heart, I am strong tonight too.
どうなっちゃってもいいじゃない
It doesn't matter what happens, does it?
際限なんてないじゃない
There are no limits, are there?
翻弄して 翻弄されて
Trifling with you, being trifled with...
ゾクゾク
It's thrilling.
喰らっちゃっても本望でしょう
Even if you take a hit, it's what you wanted, right?
最低だって滾るでしょう
Even at the worst, it gets your blood boiling, doesn't it?
見透かして 見透かされて
Seeing through me, being seen through...
Yeah yeah 終わりはない
Yeah yeah, there is no end.
高鳴るこの全てがノンフィクション
This heart-pounding everything is non-fiction.
落ちても昇ってもノンフィクション
Whether I fall or rise, it's non-fiction.
中川に浮かぶ
Floating on the Nakagawa River,
夕陽をめがけて
Aiming for the setting sun,
小石を蹴ったら
When I kicked a pebble,
靴まで飛んで
My shoe flew off with it.
ジョギングしていた
It hit the head carpenter
大工の頭に
Who was jogging by,
ガキのまんまだと
And he laughed at me,
笑われたのさ
Saying I'm still just a brat.
どこかに元気を
Even if I dropped my spirits
落っことしても
Somewhere along the way,
葛飾亀有 アクビをひとつ
Katsushika Kameari, I let out a yawn.
変わらない町並みが
The unchanging townscape
妙に優しいよ
Is strangely kind to me.
中央広場で
In the central square,
子供の手を引く
Leading a child by the hand,
太ったあの娘は
That chubby girl over there,
初恋の人
She was my first love.
権八池で
At Gonpachi Pond,
私はフラれた
I got dumped.
今でも持ってると
When I said I still have feelings,
からかわれたよ
She just teased me.
何もいいこと
Even though nothing good
なかったけれど
Happened at all,
葛飾水元 流れる雲と
Katsushika Mizumoto, with the drifting clouds,
ラプソディー口ずさみ
Humming a rhapsody,
少し歩こうか
Shall we walk a little?
カラスが鳴くから
Since the crows are cawing,
もう日が暮れるね
The sun is setting soon.
焼き鳥ほおばり
Stuffing our cheeks with yakitori,
ビール飲もうか
Shall we have a beer?
トンガリ帽子の
From the pointed-roof
取水塔から
Water intake tower,
帝釈天へと
Towards Taishakuten Temple,
夕陽が落ちる
The setting sun falls.
明日もこうして終わるんだね
Tomorrow will end like this too, won't it?
隠し事はまた 幸せだって
They say secrets are happiness too.
隠して気がついた
I realized it by hiding it,
馬鹿な本音だから
Because it's a foolish true feeling.
どこかに元気を落としても
Even if I drop my energy somewhere,
葛飾亀有
Katsushika Kameari,
あくびをひとつ
With a single yawn,
変わらない町並みが
The unchanging townscape,
妙に優しいよ
Is strangely kind.
アキロゼ生誕祭2026をご覧の皆さん
Everyone watching AkiRose Birthday Festival 2026,
いかがでしたでしょうか
How was it?
さてここからは 大事なお知らせがあるので
Now, there are important announcements,
最後までしっかり聞いていってね
So please listen carefully until the end.
まずはお知らせ一つ目
First, announcement number one.
アキ・ローゼンタール2026誕生日グッズ発売です！
Aki Rosenthal 2026 Birthday Goods are on sale!
今回はライブの世界観をぎゅっと楽しんでもらえるグッズを 頑張って制作いたしました
I worked hard to create goods that let you fully enjoy the world of the live concert.
なので今回のライブが良かったなーって思った方は
So if you thought this concert was good,
ぜひ応援で購入していただくのもすごく嬉しいです
I'd be very happy if you purchased them as support.
それではまず一つ目のグッズ
Now, the first item.
Life is GAME ラバーマット
Life is GAME Rubber Mat.
今回のイラストはLAM先生に描き下ろしていただきました
This illustration was newly drawn by LAM-sensei.
素敵なイラストありがとうございます
Thank you for the wonderful illustration.
今回のライブの世界観をイメージしたイラストになっています
It's an illustration imagining the world of this live concert.
めちゃくちゃセクシーで色っぽいけど かっこいいようなアキロゼになっています
It features an extremely sexy, alluring, yet cool AkiRose.
ラバーマットで思う存分堪能してください
Please enjoy it to your heart's content with the Rubber Mat.
ちなみにサイズはカードゲームにぴったり
By the way, the size is perfect for card games.
この意味 わかるよね？
You know what this means, right?
二つ目のグッズが
The second item is,
運命の5枚 タロット風アクリルスタンドセット
Fate's 5 Cards: Tarot-style Acrylic Stand Set.
アキロゼがあなたのことを占って背中を押してあげます
AkiRose will tell your fortune and give you a push.
一日の始まりや 何か運命を託したいみたいなそんな時に
At the start of the day or when you want to entrust your fate,
使って楽しむ
Use it and enjoy.
そして5枚バーンって飾っておけるので 見ても楽しめるようになっております
And since you can display all 5 cards boldly, it's visually enjoyable too.
占い方法は
The fortune-telling method
この後紹介するアキロゼのASMRボイスと連動しております
Is linked with AkiRose's ASMR Voice which I'll introduce next.
飾っても楽しい 使っても楽しい
Fun to display, fun to use.
そのような連動グッズになっているので ぜひゲットしてください
Please get these linked goods.
続いてのグッズは
The next item is,
アキロゼのトランプ
AkiRose's Playing Cards.
作っちゃいました
I made them!
こちら実際に遊んでいただけるトランプなので
These are playing cards you can actually play with,
たくさん予備も買った方がいいんじゃないかなと思います
So I think you should probably buy lots of spares too.
ぜひトランプでもアキロゼをたくさん楽しんで アピールもしてくださいね
Please enjoy AkiRose a lot with the playing cards and show them off.
続いてはこちら
Next is this,
アキロゼのカードケース
AkiRose's Card Case.
ホロカはもちろん トランプなど小物入れても大丈夫です
Perfect for Holo Cards, of course, but also for playing cards and small items.
ぜひお家や持ち歩きに使ってね
Please use it at home or on the go.
そしてボイスの紹介です
And now introducing the Voice.
今回もASMRボイスを特別に発売
This time too, a special release of ASMR Voice!
アキとロゼがそれぞれ左右からあなたのことを誘惑しちゃうかも
Aki and Rose might seduce you from the left and right.
台本も頑張って書いたので ぜひぜひたっぷり楽しんでもらったら嬉しいです
I worked hard writing the script, so I hope you enjoy it thoroughly.
こちらボイスは「Life is GAME ~アキとロゼの盤上~」
This Voice is 'Life is GAME ~On the Board of Aki and Rose~'.
こちらをメインとし
With this as the main,
ASMRショートボイスとして
As an ASMR Short Voice,
先ほどの運命の5枚タロット風アクリルカードと 連動したショートボイスが入っております
It contains short voices linked with the 'Fate's 5 Cards' Acrylic Set mentioned earlier.
ショートボイスのシャッフルランダム再生をして
Shuffle play the short voices,
選ばれたボイスがあなたの運命の一枚になります
And the chosen voice becomes your card of destiny.
ぜひいろいろ楽しんでね
Please enjoy it in various ways.
これらのグッズ全てが詰まったフルセット購入には なんと特典もついております
For purchasing the Full Set containing all these goods, there is a bonus included!
今回のキービジュアルのイラストを使った チケット風カードになっております
It's a ticket-style card using this key visual illustration.
あなたはこのゲームに参加する？
Will you participate in this game?
参加しない？
Or not?
こちらもライブの世界観を高めるアイテムになっているので ぜひゲットしてください
This is also an item that enhances the world of the live concert, so please get it.
そして数量限定あります
And there is a limited quantity version.
直筆サインと箔押し複製メッセージが入ったものになっております
It includes a handwritten signature and a foil-stamped duplicated message.
頑張って書きます
I will do my best to sign them.
そして数量限定が終わり次第
And once the limited quantity ends,
箔押しでの複製サインとメッセージが入った チケット風カードになります
It will become a ticket-style card with a foil-stamped duplicated signature and message.
ぜひフルセット購入特典ゲットしてね
Please get the Full Set purchase bonus.
大事な発売時間は
The important release time is,
この後21時30分
Coming up at 21:30.
21時30分にショップオープンです
The shop opens at 21:30.
ぜひ登録など準備して備えておいてね
Please register and get ready.
続きましてお知らせ二つ目
Next, announcement number two.
この後21時45分から メンバー限定のアフターライブを行います
After this, starting at 21:45, I will hold a Member-Only After Live.
ライブ本編とはまた違う楽曲を披露する予定なので ぜひお楽しみに
I plan to perform different songs from the main live, so please look forward to it.
今日メンバーになった方もぜひぜひ見てね
Those who became members today, please watch it too.
ちなみに
By the way,
過去のライブのメンバー限定アフターライブも 見れちゃうと思うので
I think you can also watch past Member-Only After Lives,
ぜひその辺も楽しんでもらえたらと思います
So I hope you enjoy those as well.
ちなみに、今回のサムネイルイラストは、メンバー限定で壁紙としてプレゼント予定です。
By the way, we plan to gift this thumbnail illustration as a wallpaper exclusively for members.
お楽しみに。
Look forward to it.
そして、お知らせ３つ目！
And, announcement number three!
本日の生誕祭ライブの後も...
Even after today's birthday live...
お楽しみはまだまだ続きます。
...the fun is far from over.
なんと、ホロアースにて特別企画
Surprisingly, a special project in HoloEarth:
『アキ・ローゼンタール生誕祭2026 アンコール in ホロアース』を開催します！
We will hold 'Aki Rosenthal Birthday Festival 2026 Encore in HoloEarth'!
今回初披露した新曲『Monopoly』を
I will sing the new song 'Monopoly', revealed for the first time today,
ホロアースで歌っちゃいます。
in HoloEarth.
いろんな角度から、アキロゼのパフォーマンスや演出をじっくりと見てみてくださいね。
Please take a good look at AkiRose's performance and production from various angles.
さらに、ホロアースだけのMCパートもたっぷりあるので
Furthermore, there's plenty of MC parts exclusive to HoloEarth,
ぜひぜひ会いに来てください。
so please, definitely come meet me.
開催日は３月１３日。
The date is March 13th.
３月１３日です。
It's March 13th.
詳細はホロアース公式Xをチェックしてね。
Check the official HoloEarth X for details.
そして、最後のお知らせが、新曲『Monopoly』！
And the final announcement is the new song 'Monopoly'!
本日日付が変わる頃にリリースされますので
It will be released around midnight tonight,
各音楽配信サービスからぜひ購入してね。
so please purchase it from music streaming services.
たくさん聴いてね。
Please listen to it a lot.
振り付けも歌もとってもキャッチーなので
Since both the choreography and song are very catchy,
覚えてみんなで楽しんでもらえる
I hope it becomes a song everyone can learn,
愛されるような楽曲になってくれたら
enjoy together, and love.
嬉しいなって思っています。
That would make me happy.
また後日ライブ配信で、新曲『Monopoly』だったり
Also, in a livestream at a later date, regarding 'Monopoly'...
今回のライブに触れた後日談など語ったり
...or stories about this live, I'd like to talk...
一緒に見たりなどしたいなと思ってるので
...and watch it together with you.
ぜひチャンネル登録、高評価ポチ！
So please subscribe, hit the like button!
通知もオン！
Turn on notifications too!
忘れてた人は、今ポチッとしてね。
If you forgot, hit that button right now.
絶対絶対また会いに来てね。
Definitely, definitely come see me again.
それでは...
Well then...
運命は時に残酷。
Fate is sometimes cruel.
あなたが選びたくて選んだものではないかもしれない。
It might not be something you chose because you wanted to.
だけど...
But...
いつでもあなたの人生は...
...at any time, your life...
あなたのもの。
...belongs to you.
人生は一度きり。
Life is a one-time thing.
やり直しのきかないこのゲーム...
This game with no resets...
あなたは、どう楽しむ？
How will you enjoy it?
Member Only After Live
END